After earning a bachelor’s degree, I was determined to do what I love.
获得学士学位后，我决心去做自己热爱的事。
I headed straight to graduate school to investigate the social problems that fascinated me.
我直接去读了研究生，探究那些令我着迷的社会问题。
For almost a decade, I told everyone I encountered that they should do the same.
将近十年间，我对遇到的每一个人都说：你也应该这样做。
“Follow your passion,” I counseled.
“追随你的激情，”我劝道。
“You can figure out the employment stuff later.”
“就业的事，你可以以后再想办法。”
It wasn’t until I began to research this widely accepted career advice that I understood how problematic it really was.
直到开始研究这条广为接受的职业建议，我才明白它其实有多大的问题。
As a sociologist, I interviewed college students and professional workers to learn what it really meant to pursue their dreams, which I will refer to here as the passion principle.
作为一名社会学家，我采访了大学生和专业人士，以了解追求自己的梦想究竟意味着什么——在本文中，我把这种追求称为“激情原则”。
I was stunned by what I found out about this principle in the research for my new book.
在为新书做研究时，我对这一原则有了一些发现，令我大为震惊。
Surveys show the American public has long held the passion principle in high regard as a career decision-making priority.
调查显示，长期以来，美国公众一直非常看重激情原则，把它视为职业决策时要优先考虑的因素。
And its popularity is even stronger among those facing job instability.
而在面临工作不稳定的人当中，这一原则甚至更受欢迎。
Advocates of the passion principle found it compelling because they believed that following one’s passion can provide workers with both the motivation necessary to work hard and a place to find fulfillment.
激情原则的拥护者认为它很有说服力，因为他们相信，追随自己的激情既能为劳动者提供努力工作所需的动力，又能给他们一方获得成就感的天地。
Yet, what I found is that following one’s passion does not necessarily lead to fulfillment, but is one of the most powerful cultural forces perpetuating overwork.
然而，我的发现是，追随自己的激情并不一定会带来成就感，却是使过度工作长期存在的最强大的文化力量之一。
I also found that promoting the pursuit of one’s passion helps perpetuate social inequalities due to the fact that not everyone has the same economic resources to allow them to pursue their passion with ease.
我还发现，提倡追求自己的激情会促使社会不平等延续下去，因为并非每个人都拥有同样的经济资源，能让自己轻松地追求激情。
While the passion principle is broadly popular, not everyone has the necessary resources to turn their passion into a stable, good-paying job.
虽然激情原则广受欢迎，但并非每个人都拥有必要的资源，能把自己的激情变成一份稳定且薪酬不错的工作。
Passion-seekers from wealthy families are better able to wait until a job they are passionate about comes along without worrying about student loans in the meantime.
出身富裕家庭的激情追求者更有条件一直等到自己热爱的工作出现，在此期间也不必为学生贷款发愁。
They are also better situated to take unpaid internships to get their foot in the door while their parents pay their rent.
他们也更有条件去做无薪实习，借此踏进行业的门槛，房租则由父母来付。
And they often have access to parents’ social networks to help them find jobs.
而且，他们往往能利用父母的社会关系网来帮自己找工作。
Surveys revealed that working-class and first-generation college graduates, regardless of their career field, are more likely than their wealthier peers to end up in low-paying unskilled jobs when they pursue their passion.
调查显示，工人阶级出身的大学毕业生和家中第一代大学毕业生在追求激情时，无论选择哪个职业领域，都比家境较富裕的同龄人更有可能最终从事低薪的非技术性工作。
Colleges, workplaces and career counselors that promote the “follow your passion” path for everyone, without leveling the playing field, help perpetuate socioeconomic inequalities among career aspirants.
高校、工作单位和职业顾问若向所有人推崇“追随你的激情”这条道路，却不营造公平的竞争环境，就会促使社会经济不平等在怀有职业抱负的人之间延续下去。
It’s not just well-off passion-seekers who benefit from the passion principle.
从激情原则中受益的，不只是家境优渥的激情追求者。
Employers of passionate workers do, too.
雇主如果拥有满怀激情的员工，也同样会从中受益。
Potential employers showed greater interest in passionate applicants in part because they believed the applicants would work hard at their jobs without expecting an increase in pay.
潜在雇主对满怀激情的求职者表现出更大的兴趣，部分原因在于他们相信，这些求职者会努力工作，而不指望加薪。
Passionate workers even sacrifice a good salary, job stability and leisure time to work in a job they love.
为了从事自己热爱的工作，满怀激情的员工甚至会牺牲不错的薪水、工作的稳定性和闲暇时间。